Neural Networks are good
神经网络有助于学
for learning lots of different types of patterns.
习许多不同类型的模式。
To give an example of how is it work
举个例子来说明它是如何工作的
imagine you had a four pixel camera.
，假设你有一个四像素的摄像头。
So not four megapixels, but just four pixels.
所以不是四百万像素，而是四个像素。
And it was only black and white.
只有黑白两色。
And you wanted to go around and take pictures of things
你想到处走走，拍拍照片
and determine automatically then
然后自动确定
whether these pictures were
这些照片是否
solid, all white or all dark image, vertical line
实心的，全白或全黑的图像，垂直线
or a diagonal line or a horizontal line?
或者一条对角线或者一条水平线？
This is tricky because you can't do this with simple rules
这是棘手的，因为你不能这样做的简单规
about the brightness of the pixels.
则的像素的亮度。
Both of these are horizontal lines,
这两条都是水平线,
but if you try to make a rule about which pixel was bright
但是，如果你试图制定一个规则，哪个像素是明亮的，
and which was dark you wouldn't be able to do it.
哪个是暗的，你就不能这样做。
So to do this with the neural network
所以要用神经网络做到这一点，
you start by taking all of your inputs,
你首先要获取你所有的输入,
in this case our four pixels,
在这个例子中，我们的四个像素,
and you break them out into input neurons.
把它们分解成输入神经元。
You assign a number to each of these
根据像素的亮度或暗度，
depending on the brightness or darkness of the pixel.
为每个像素分配一个数字。
+1 is all the way white. -1 is all the way black.
+ 1是所有的白色-1是所有的黑色。
And then gray is zero right in the middle.
中间的灰色为零。
So these values once you have them broken out
一旦你把这些值分解出来，像这
and listed like this on the input neurons,
样列在输入神经元上,
It's also called the input vector or array.
它也被称为输入向量或数组。
It's just a list of numbers
它只是一个代
that represents your inputs right now.
表你现在输入的数字列表。
It's a useful notion to think about
考虑神经元的接收区
the receptive field of a neuron.
是一个有用的概念。
All this means is what set of inputs
所有这一切意味着什么样的输入
makes the value of this neuron as high as it can possibly be.
设置使这个神经元的价值尽可能高。
For input neurons this is pretty easy.
对于输入神经元来说，这是相当容易的。
Each one is associated with just one pixel
每个神经元只与一个像素相
and when that pixel is all the way white
关联，当这个像素全部为白色时
the value of that input neuron is as high as it could go.
，输入神经元的值就会达到最高值。
The black and white checkered areas show pixels
黑白方格区域显示输入
that an input neuron doesn't care about.
神经元不关心的像素。
If they're all the way white or all the way black
如果它们全部都是白色或者
it still doesn't affect the value of that input on it all.
全部都是黑色，它仍然不会影响所有输入的值。
Now to build a neural network we create a neuron.
现在，为了构建一个神经网络，我们创建了一个神经元。
The first thing this does is it adds up
这样做的第一件事就是
all of the values of the input neurons.
把所有输入神经元的值加起来。
So in this case if we add up all of those values we get a 0.50
所以在这种情况下，如果我们把所有这些值加起来，我们得到0.50
Now to complicate things just a little bit
现在把事情复杂化
each of the connections are weighted
一点，每个连接都是加权的，
meaning they're multiplied by a number.
意思是它们被乘以一个数。
That number can be 1 or -1 or anything in between.
这个数字可以是1或者 -1，或者介于两者之间的任何数字。
So for instance if something has a weight of -1
举个例子，如果某个物体的
its multiplied and you get the negative of it.
重量是-1，它就会乘以它的负数。
And that's added in.
而且还要加进去。
If something has a weight of zero
如果某物的重量为零，
then it's effectively ignored.
那么它就被有效地忽略了。
So here's what those weighted connections might look like.
这就是这些加权连接可能的样子。
You'll notice that after the values of the input neurons
你会注意到，在输入神经元的值被加权并
are weighted and added
且加上这些值之后..
the values come... the final value is completely different.
. ... 最终的值是完全不同的。
Graphically it's convenient to represent these weights
用图形来表示这些权重是很方便的
as white links being positive weights
白色链接是正权重
black links being negative weights
黑色链接是负重量
and the thickness of the line
还有线条的粗细
is roughly proportional to the magnitude of the weight.
大致与重量成正比。
Then after you add the weighted input neurons
然后加上加权输入神经元，它们就被压
they get squashed and I'll show you what that means.
扁了，我会向你们展示这意味着什么。
You have a sigmoid squashing function.
你有一个 s 形挤压函数。
Sigmoid just means S-shaped.
S 形的意思就是 s 形。
And what this does is you put a value in,
这样做的目的就是把一个值放进去,
let's say 0.5
就算0.5吧
And you run a vertical line up to your sigmoid
然后你沿着一条直线跑到你的乙状结肠
and then a horizontal line over
然后是一条水平线
from where it crosses
从它穿过的地方
and then where that hits the Y-axis
然后到达 y 轴
that's the output of your function.
这就是你功能的输出。
So in this case slightly less than point five.
所以在这个例子中略低于0.5。
It's pretty close.
很接近了。
As your input number gets larger
随着输入数量的增加，
output number also gets larger, but more slowly.
输出数量也会增加，但速度会变慢。
And eventually,
最终,
no matter how big the number you put in
不管你输入的数字
the answer is always less than one.
有多大，答案总是小于1。
Similarly when you go negative
同样，当你消极的时候
the answer is always greater than negative one.
，答案总是大于消极的。
So this ensures that neurons value
因此，这保证了神经元的
never gets outside of the range of +1 to -1
值永远不会超出 + 1到
which is helpful for keeping the computations
-1的范围，这有助于保持神经网
in the neural network bounded and stable.
络中的计算有界和稳定。
So after you sum the weighted values of neurons
所以当你把神经元的加权值加起来
squash the result -- you get the output.
之后，你就得到了输出。
In this case 0.746
在这种情况下，
That is a neuron.
这是一个神经元。
So we can call this...
所以我们可以称之为..。
we can collapse all that down and this is a neuron
我们可以把这些都倒下，这是一个做加权和
that does a weighted sum and squash the result.
运算的神经元，然后压缩结果。
And now instead of just one of those
现在不再是只有一个假设你
assume you have a whole bunch
有一大堆，
there are 4 shown here, but there could be 400 or 4 million.
而是有4个，但是可能有400或400万。
Now to keep our picture clear we'll assume for now
现在为了让我们的图片更清晰，我们假
that the weights are either +1, white lines,
设现在的权重要么是 + 1，白线,
-1, black lines,
- 1，黑线,
or 0, which case they're missing entirely.
或者0，这种情况下，他们完全失踪。
But in actuality all of these neurons that we created
但实际上，我们创造的所有这些神经元，
are each attached to all of the input neurons
都附着在所有的输入神经元上，
and they all have some weight between -1 and +1.
它们的权重都在 -1和 + 1之间。
When we create this first layer of our neural network
当我们创建神经网络的第一层时
the receptive fields get more complex.
，感受域变得更加复杂。
For instance here each of those
例如，这里每个神经元最终结合
end up combining two of our input neurons
了我们的两个输入神经元，所以这个值.
and so the value... the receptive field...
.. ... 接收区... ..。
the pixel values that make that first layer neuron,
构成第一层神经元的像素值,
as large as it can possibly be,
尽可能的大,
look now like pairs of pixels.
现在看起来像一对对的像素。
Either all white or a mixture of white and black
根据重量的不同，可以是全白的，也可
depending on the weights.
以是黑白混合的。
So for instance this neuron here
例如，这个神经元连接到
is attached to this input pixel (which is upper-left)
这个输入像素(左上角)和这个输入
and this input pixel (just lower left)
像素(左下角) ，
and both of those weights are positive.
这两个权重都是正值。
So it combines the two of those.
所以它结合了这两者。
And that's it's receptive field.
这是一个接受的领域。
The receptive field of this one
这一个的感受野加
plus the receptive field of this one.
上这一个的感受野。
However, if we look at this neuron
然而，如果我们观
it combines...
察这个神经元，它结合了..。
this pixel upper right and this pixel lower right.
右上角的像素，右下角的像素。
It has a weight of minus one for the lower right pixel
右下角的像素的重量为负一，这意
so that means it's most active when this pixel is black,
味着当这个像素是黑色时，它是最活跃的,
so here is its receptive field.
这里是它的感受野。
Now because we were careful
现在，因为我们小心地创
of how we created that first layer
建了第一层，
its values look a lot like input values.
它的值看起来很像输入值。
And we can turn right around and create another layer
我们可以右转，在上面再创建一个
on top of it the exact same way
图层，同样的方式，
with the output of one layer being the input to the next layer.
一个图层的输出就是下一个图层的输入。
And we can repeat this three times or seven times
我们可以重复这个过程三次，七次
or 700 times for additional layers.
，或者700次。
Each time the receptive fields get even more complex.
每次感受野变得更加复杂。
So you can see here using the same logic
所以你可以看到这里使用相
now they cover all of the pixels
同的逻辑现在他们覆盖了所有的
and more special arrangement
像素和更多的特殊安排，其中
of which are black and which are white.
是黑色和白色的。
We can create another layer...
我们可以创建另一个图层..。
Again all of these neurons in one layer are connected
同样，在一层的所有这些神经元都连接到前
to all of the neurons in the previous layer.
一层的所有神经元。
But we're assuming here
但是我们在这里假设大部分
that most of those weights are zero and not shown.
的权重都是零，并且没有显示出来。
It's not generally the case.
事实并非如此。
So just to mix things up, we'll create a new layer,
所以为了混合起来，我们要创建一个新的层,
but if you notice our squashing function isn't there anymore.
但是如果你注意到我们的挤压功能已经不存在了。
We have something new called a rectified linear unit.
我们有一个新的东西，叫做整流线性单位。
This is another popular neuron type.
这是另一种流行的神经元类型。
So you do your weighted sum of all your inputs
所以你做你所有输入的加
and instead of squashing you do rectified linear units.
权和，而不是挤压你做整流线性单位。
You rectify it.
你去纠正它。
So if it is negative you make the value 0.
所以如果是负数，那么值就是0。
If it's positive you keep the value.
如果它是正值，你就保持它的值。
This is obviously very easy to compute
这显然是非常容易计算，并证明
and it turns out to have very nice stability properties
它有非常好的稳定性属性，为神经网
for neural networks as well.
络以及。
In practice.
实际上。
So after we do this because some of our weights are positive
因为有些重量是正的，有些
and some are negative,
是负的,
connecting to those rectified linear units,
连接到那些校正的线性单位,
we get receptive fields and their opposites.
我们有接受能量场和它们的对立面。
Look at the patterns there.
看看这些图案。
And then finally when we've created as many layers
最后，当我们创建了尽可能多的
with as many neurons as we want
神经元层，我们创
we create an output layer.
建了一个输出层。
Here we have four outputs that we're interested in.
这里我们有四个我们感兴趣的输出。
Is the image solid, vertical, diagonal or horizontal.
图像是实心的、垂直的、对角线的还是水平的。
So to walk through an example here
我们来看一个
of how this would work,
例子,
let's say we start with this input image
假设我们从左边的输入
shown on the left.
图像开始。
Dark pixels on top, white on the bottom.
上面是黑色的像素，下面是白色的。
As we propagate that to our input layer
当我们把它传播到我们的输入层时，
this is what those values would look like.
这就是那些值的样子。
The top pixels, the bottom pixels.
顶部像素，底部像素。
As we move that to our first layer
当我们移动到我们的第一层，
we can see the combination of a dark pixel
我们可以看到一个黑色像素和一个光
and a light pixel summed together
色像素的组合在一起得到
get us zero -- gray.
我们的零——灰色。
Whereas down here we have
然而在这里，
the combination of a dark pixel
我们有一个黑色像素和
plus a light pixel with a negative weight.
一个负重量的亮像素的组合。
So that gets us a value of negative one here.
所以这里我们得到了一个负1的值。
Which makes sense
这是有道理的
because if we look at the receptive field here...
，因为如果我们看看这里的感受域..。
Upper left pixel white,
左上角白色像素,
lower left pixel black.
左下黑色像素。
This the exact opposite of the input that we're getting
这与我们得到的输入正好相反，所以
and so we would expect its value to be as low as possible.
我们希望它的值尽可能的低。
Minus one.
减去一。
As we move to the next layer
当我们移动到下一层，
we see the same types of things.
我们看到相同类型的东西。
Combining zeros to get zeros.
组合零得到零。
Combining a negative and a negative with a negative weight
把一个负的、一个负的和一个负的重量结合起来
which makes a positive to get a zero.
，使得一个正的得到一个零。
And here we have combining two negatives to get a negative.
这里我们把两个负数结合起来得到一个负数。
So again you'll notice the receptive field of this
所以你们会再次注意到，这个接受
is exactly the inverse of our input.
域正好与我们的输入相反。
So it makes sense that it's weight would be negative.
所以它的重量是负值是有道理的。
Or its value would be negative.
否则它的价值将是负数。
And we move to the next layer.
然后我们进入下一层。
All of these, of course, these zeros propagate forward.
当然，所有这些零都是向前传播的。
Here...
给你。
This is a negative has a negative value,
这是一个负值,
and it gets... has a positive weight.
它的重量是正的。
So it just moves straight forward.
所以它只是直接向前移动。
Because we have a rectified linear unit,
因为我们有一个矫正的线性单位,
negative values become zero.
负值变成零。
So now it is zero again too.
所以现在它又是零了。
But this one gets rectified and becomes positive.
但是这一点得到纠正，变得积极。
Negative times a negative is positive.
负数乘以负数就是正数。
And so when we finally get to the output
所以当我们最终得到输出时，
we can see they're all zero except for this horizontal,
我们可以看到除了这个水平面，它们都是零,
which is positive, and that's the answer.
这是积极的，这就是答案。
Our neural network said
我们的神经网
this is an image of a horizontal line.
络说这是一条水平线的图像。
Now, neural networks usually aren't that good,
神经网络通常不是那么好,
not that clean.
没那么干净。
So there's a notion of with an input what is truth?
所以输入的概念是什么是真理？
In this case the truth is
在这个例子中
this has a zero for all of these values,
，所有这些值都是0,
but a one for horizontal.
而是水平方向的。
It's not solid. It's not vertical. It's not diagonal.
它不是实心的，不是垂直的，不是对角线的。
Yes, it is horizontal.
是的，它是水平的。
An arbitrary neural network will give answers
任意的神经网络会给出不完全正
that are not exactly truth.
确的答案。
It might be off by a little or a lot.
它可能会偏离一点或者很多。
And then the error is the magnitude of the difference
然后这个错误就是真相和给出的答
between the truth and the answer given.
案之间的差距。
And you can add all these up
你可以把所有这些加
to get the total error for the neural network.
起来，得到神经网络的总误差。
So the idea...
所以这个想法..。
the whole idea with learning and training
学习和训练的整个思
is to adjust the weights
想就是调整权
to make the error as low as possible.
重使误差尽可能小。
So the way this is done is...
所以做这件事的方法是..。
Put an image in we calculate the error at the end,
把一个图像放进去，我们计算最后的误差,
then we look for how to adjust those weights
然后我们寻找如何调整这
higher or lower to either make that error go up or down.
些权重或高或低，使误差上升或下降。
And we of course adjust the weights in the way
我们当然要调整权重，而不
than make the error go down.
是降低误差。
Now, the problem with doing this
现在，这样做的问题是，
is each time we go back and calculate the error
每次我们回去计算误差，
we have to multiply all of those weights
我们必须把所有的权重乘
by all of the neurons values at each layer.
以每层的所有神经元值。
And we have to do that again and again
对于每个重量，我们必须
once for each weight.
一次又一次地这样做。
This takes forever in computing terms
在计算规模的计算术语中，这需要
on computing scale.
永远的时间。
And so it's not a practical way
所以这不是一个训练大型神
to train a big neural network.
经网络的实用方法。
You can imagine instead of just rolling down
你可以想象，我们不仅仅是滚到一个简
to the bottom of a simple valley
单的山谷的底部，我们还
we have a very high dimensional valley
有一个非常高维度的山谷，我们必须
and we have to find our way down.
找到我们的方式下降。
And because there are so many dimensions
因为每个权重都有
one for each of these weights
如此多的维度
that the computation just becomes prohibitively expensive.
，以至于计算过程变得非常昂贵。
Luckily there was an insight
幸运的是有一个洞察力可以
that lets us do this in a very reasonable time,
让我们在合理的时间内做到这一点,
and that's that if we're careful about
如果我们仔细设计我们的神
how we design our neural network
经网络，我们
we can calculate this slope directly.
可以直接计算这个斜率。
The gradient.
梯度。
We can figure out the direction
我们可以找出我们需要
that we need to adjust the weight
调整重量的方向，
without going all the way back
而不需要通过我们的
through our neural network and recalculating.
神经网络重新计算。
So just review,
所以回顾一下,
the slope that we're talking about is
我们所说的斜率是
when we make a change in weight
当我们改变重量的时候
the error will change a little bit
错误会改变一点点
and that relation of the change in weight
重量变化的关系
to the change in error is the slope.
误差的变化是斜率。
Mathematically there are several ways to write this.
数学上有几种写这个的方法。
I will favor the one on the bottom.
我喜欢底下那个。
It's technically most correct.
这在技术上是最正确的。
We'll call it DE/DW for shorthand.
我们将它简称为 de / dw。
Every time you see it, just think:
每次你看到它的时候，就想: “
"The change in error when I change a weight"
当我改变一个重量的时候，错误的改变”
Or the change in the thing on the top
或者是顶部的变化，当我
when I change the thing on the bottom.
改变底部的变化时。
This does get us into a little bit of calculus,
这确实让我们进入了一点微积分,
we do take derivatives.
我们求导数。
It's how we calculate slope.
这是我们计算斜率的方法。
If it's new to you
如果你还没学过
I strongly recommend a good semester of calculus.
，我强烈推荐你学一个好学期的微积分。
Just because the concepts are so universal
只是因为这些概念是如此普遍，
and a lot of them have very nice physical interpretations,
而且许多概念都有非常好的物理解释,
which I find very appealing.
我觉得很有吸引力。
But don't worry
但不要担心，
otherwise just gloss over this
否则只是掩盖这一点，
and pay attention to the rest,
注意其余的,
and you'll get a general sense for how this works.
你就能大致了解这是怎么回事了。
So in this case if we change the weight by +1,
在这种情况下，如果我们把权重改为 + 1,
the error changes by -2,
误差变化为 -2,
which gives us a slope of minus two.
这样就得到了负2的斜率。
That tells us the direction
这告诉我们，我们应该调整我
that we should adjust our weight
们的重量的方向，
and how much we should adjust it
以及我们应该调整多少，
to bring the error down.
以减少误差。
Now to do this you have to know
要做到这一点，你必须知道
what your error function is.
你的错误函数是什么。
So assume we had error function
假设我们有误差函数，
that was the square of the weight.
就是权重的平方。
And you can see that our weight is right at -1.
你们可以看到我们的重量正好是 -1。
So the first thing we do is we take the derivative,
我们要做的第一件事就是求导,
change in error divided by change in weight, DE/DW.
误差变化除以权重变化，de / dw。
The derivative of weight squared is two times the weight
重量平方的导数等于重量的2倍，所以我
and so we plug in our weight of -1
们把我们的重量加进去，
and we get a slope DE/DW of minus two.
得到斜率 de / dw 等于 -2。
Now the other trick
现在，另一个让
that lets us do this with deep neural networks
我们用深层神经网络做到这一点
is chaining.
的技巧是链接。
And to show you how this works
为了展示它是如何工
imagine a very simple trivial neural network
作的，想象一个只有一个隐藏层
with just one hidden layer,
的非常简单的神经网络,
one input layer, one output layer
一个输入层，一个输出
and one weight connecting each of them.
层和一个权重连接它们。
So it's obvious to see
很明显，y
that the value Y
的值就是
is just the value X times the weight connecting them.
x 乘以连接它们的权重。
W1.
So if we change W1 a little bit,
所以如果我们稍微改变一下 W1,
we just take the derivative of Y with respect to W1,
我们只需求 y 对 W1的导数,
that we get X, the slope is X.
我们得到 x，斜率是 x。
If I change W1 by a little bit
如果我把 W1改变一点点
then Y will change by X times the size of that adjustment.
，那么 y 就会改变 x 乘以那个调整的大小。
Similarly for the next step.
下一步也是如此。
You can see that E
你可以看到
is just the value Y times the weight W2.
e 就是 y 乘以重量 W2。
And so when we calculate DE/DY it's just W2.
所以当我们计算 de / dy 时，它只是 W2。
Because this network is so simple
因为这个网络非常简单
we can calculate from one end to the other
，我们可以从一端计算到另一端
X times W1 times W2 is the error E.
X 乘以 W1乘以 W2是误差 e。
And so if we want to calculate
所以如果我们想计算，如果
how much will the error change if I change W1,
我改变 W1，误差会有多大变化,
we just take the derivative of that with respect to W1
我们对 W1求导，得到
and get X times W2.
x 乘以 W2。
So this illustrates, you can see here now,
这说明，你现在可以看到,
that what we just calculated
我们刚才计
is actually the product of our first derivative
算的实际上是我们一阶导数的
that we took,
乘积,
DY/DW1,
dy / dw1,
times the derivative for the next step,
乘以下一步的导数,
the DE/DY,
de / dy,
multiplied together.
相乘。
This is chaining.
这就是链接。
You can calculate the slope of each tiny step
你可以计算每一个小步骤的
and then multiply all of those together
斜率，然后把所有的斜率相
to get the slope of the full chain...
乘得到整个链的斜率..。
the derivative of the full chain.
完整链的导数。
So in a deeper neural network
所以在更深层的神
what this would look like is
经网络中，如果我
if I want to know
想知道
how much the error will change
如果我调整网络
if I adjust a weight that's deep in the network,
深处的权重，错误会改变多少,
I just calculate the derivative of each tiny little step.
我只是计算每一小步的导数。
All the way back
回到我正在
to the weight that I'm trying to calculate.
计算的重量。
And then multiply them all together.
然后把它们放在一起。
This computationally is many many times cheaper
这种计算方法比我们在重新计算
than what we had to do before
每个重量的整个
of recalculating the error for the whole neural network
神经网络的误差之前要便
for every weight.
宜很多倍。
Now, in the neural network that we've created
现在，在我们创建的神经网
there are several types of
络中，有几种类型的反向传
back propagation we have to do.
播我们必须做。
There are several operations we have to do.
我们还有几个手术要做。
For each one of those
对于其中的每一个
we have to be able to calculate the slope.
，我们必须能够计算出斜率。
So for the first one is just a weighted connection
所以对于第一个，只是两个神经元 a
between two neurons A and B.
和 b 之间的加权连接。
So let's assume we know
假设我们知道 b
the change in error with respect to B.
的误差变化。
We want to know
我们想知道
the change in error with respect to A.
a 的误差变化。
To get there we need to know DB/DA.
为了达到这个目标，我们需要了解 db / da。
So to get that we just write
为了得到这个结果，我们只
the relationship between B and A.
需要写 b 和 a 之间的关系。
Take the derivative of B with respect to A
求 b 关于 a 的导数，
you get the weight W
得到重量 w，
and now we know how to make that step.
现在我们知道怎么做了。
We know how to do that little nugget
我们知道如何做这个小小
of back propagation.
的反向传播。
Another element that we've seen is sums.
我们看到的另一个元素是求和。
All of our neurons sum up a lot of inputs.
我们所有的神经元总结了大量的输入信息。
To take this back propagation step
为了执行这个反向传播步骤，
we do the same thing.
我们做同样的事情。
We write our expression
我们写出
and then we take the derivative of our endpoint Z
表达式，然后对端点 z 对
with respect to a step
传播到 a
that we are propagating to A.
的步骤求导。
And DZ/DA in this case is just 1.
在这种情况下，dz / da 是1。
Which make sense
如果我们
if we have a sum of a whole bunch of elements,
有一堆元素的总和,
we increase one of those elements by one,
我们将其中一种元素增加一倍,
we expect the sum to increase by one.
我们预计总和会增加1。
That's the definition of a slope of one.
这就是一个斜率的定义。
One-to-one relation there.
一对一的关系。
Another element that we have,
我们还有另外一个元素,
that we need to be able to back propagate
我们需要能够反向繁
is the sigmoid function.
殖的 S形函数。
So this one's a little bit more interesting mathematically.
所以这个在数学上更有趣一点。
I'll just write it shorthand like this, the sigma function.
我会把它写成这样的速记，sigma 函数。
It is entirely feasible to go through
这是完全可行的经过，并采
and take the derivative of this analytically
取导数的这个分
and calculate it.
析和计算它。
It just so happens that this function has a nice property
这个函数有一个很好的性质，要得到
that to get its derivative
它的导数，你只
you just multiply it by one minus itself.
需要把它乘以1减去它本身。
So this is very straightforward to calculate.
所以这是非常简单的计算。
Another element that we've used
我们使用的另一个元
is the rectified linear unit.
素是整流线性单位。
Again to figure out how to back propagate this
为了找到反向传播的方法，
we just write out the relation
我们只要写出，如果
B is equal to A if a is positive, otherwise it's zero.
a 是正的，关系式 b 等于 a，否则为零。
And piecewise for each of those we take the derivative.
对于每一个，我们求导。
So DB/DA is either one if a is positive or zero.
所以如果 a 为正或者为零，db / da 就是1。
And so with all of these
所以所有这些
little back propagation steps
小小的反向传播步骤
and the ability to chain them together
以及将它们连接在一起的能力
we can calculate the effect
我们可以计算出影响
of adjusting any given weight on the error
调整任何给定权重的错误
for any given input.
任何给定的输入。
And so to train then.
然后就开始训练。
We start with a fully connected network.
我们从一个完全连接的网络开始。
We don't know what any of these weights should be.
我们不知道这些重量应该是多少。
And so we assign them all random values.
所以我们给它们分配所有的随机值。
We create a completely arbitrary random neural network.
我们创建了一个完全任意的随机神经网络。
We put in an input
我们输入我们
that we know the answer to.
知道答案的信息。
We know whether it's solid,
我们知道它是否是固体,
vertical, diagonal or horizontal.
垂直的，对角的或者水平的。
So we know what truth should be
所以我们知道真理应该是什么
and so we can calculate the error.
，所以我们可以计算错误。
Then...
然后..。
we run it through calculate the error
我们运行它通过计算误
and using back propagation
差和使用反
go through and adjust all of those weights
向传播通过，并调整所有这些权
a tiny bit in the right direction.
重一点点在正确的方向。
And then we do that again
然后我们用另一个输
with another input,
入再做一次,
and again with another input for...
还有另外一个输入..。
If we can get away with it
如果我们可以逃
many thousands or even millions of times.
避成千上万次，甚至上百万次。
And eventually all of those weights will gravitate,
最终所有的重量都会被吸引,
they'll roll down that many dimensional valley
它们会从多维山谷滚下来，
to a nice low spot in the bottom.
到底部一个很好的低点。
Where it performs really well
它表现得非常好，
and does pretty close to truth on most of the images.
并且在大多数图像上都非常接近真实。
If we're really lucky
如果我们真的很幸运，
it will look like what we started with.
它将看起来像我们开始时的样子。
With intuitively... understandable receptive fields
凭直觉... ... 可以理解的感受域
for those neurons
和一个相
and a relatively sparse representation
对稀疏的表示意味着
meaning that most of the weights
大多数权
are small or close to zero.
重是小或接近零。
That doesn't always turn out that way.
但事实并非总是如此。
But what we aren't guaranteed
但是我们不能保证
is it'll find a pretty good representation of...
它会找到一个很好的代表..。
you know, the best that it can do
你知道，它所能做的
adjusting those weights to get as close as possible
最好的就是调整这些权重，使它尽可能接
to the right answer for all of the inputs.
近所有输入的正确答案。
So what we've covered is just a very basic introduction
所以我们所讨论的只是对神经网络
to the principles behind neural networks.
背后原理的一个非常基本的介绍。
I haven't told you quite enough
我告诉你的还不够多，
to be able to go out and build one of your own.
还不足以让你走出去自己造一个。
But if you're feeling motivated to do so
但是如果你有动力这样做，
I highly encourage it.
我强烈鼓励你这样做。
Here are a few resources that you'll find useful.
这里有一些你会发现有用的资源。
You'll want to go and learn about biased neurons.
你会想去学习有偏见的神经元。
Dropout is a useful training tool.
辍学是一个有用的培训工具。
There are several resources available
有几个可用的资源，从安德
from Andrej Karpathy
烈卡帕西，他是
who is an expert in neural networks
一个专家在神经网络和
and great at teaching about it.
伟大的教学关于它。
Also there's a fantastic article
还有一篇很棒的文章叫做
called "The Black Magic of Deep Learning"
“深度学习的黑魔法” ，
that just has a bunch of practical "from the trenches" tips
里面有一些实用的“来自战壕”的技巧，告诉你
on how to get them working well.
如何让他们更好的工作。
If you found this useful,
如果你觉得这个有用,
I highly encourage you to visit my blog
我强烈鼓励你访问我的博客
and check out several other "how it works" style posts.
，并检查其他几个“它如何工作”的风格文章。
And the links for these slides you can get as well
这些幻灯片的链接你也
to use however you like.
可以随意使用。
There's also link to them down in the comment section.
在下面的评论部分也有他们的链接。
Thanks for listening.
谢谢你的聆听。